{
    "id": "b07d1b9646614068a86ef782979ec471",
    "title": "Conditional Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. run into Jake, tell him that he owes me 100 dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3bea2478c39e4373875c339b2e016ff8"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had another 1000 dollars, I ………………… a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can buy",
                "could buy",
                "could have bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7921450dd71a410bb216c8e41638a98c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he should be late, we ……………….. to go without him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "would have",
                "could have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d23d1068a9c64e3f8bd7900f69417e37"
        },
        {
            "question": "What would you do if you ………………… to lose your job?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0e04edcc9894d80849df6e782bd7ce0"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. to move a bit, I could sit here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "437767d300074fdbb6aed8cfcadae0d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Had I realized what you intended, I ………………….. this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not permit",
                "would not permit",
                "would not have permitted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b8a43ec4c665464a8eb6e82fe12e2756"
        },
        {
            "question": "Were she my daughter, I …………………… her wear that mini-frock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not let",
                "would not let",
                "would not have let"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8947d632152d4a199daaf8d60b4e019e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. finish early, give me a ring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "happen to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6d126c98dd4e4da7b2b4c0336189e240"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will get up earlier if there ………………… a good reason to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "826af981c6224b2fa5bc005a65511f5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It would be nice if you …………………. me a few dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "lent",
                "would lend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4779aede58a74cabb0574ece35cdd31e"
        }
    ]
}